const HabitatsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What type of habitat is characterized by extremely cold temperatures and little vegetation?",
        options: ["Tundra", "Desert", "Rainforest"],
        correct_option: "Tundra"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat is known for its high temperatures, sand dunes, and cacti?",
        options: ["Tundra","Desert",  "Ocean"],
        correct_option: "Desert"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat contains the most diverse range of plant and animal species?",
        options: ["Rainforest", "Grassland", "Mountain"],
        correct_option: "Rainforest"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat is characterized by tall grasses and few trees?",
        options: ["Grassland", "Desert", "Tundra"],
        correct_option: "Grassland"
    },
    {
        question: "What habitat is characterized by its large, flowing bodies of water?",
        options: ["Ocean", "Tundra","Freshwater", ],
        correct_option: "Freshwater"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat is characterized by its extreme temperatures and lack of vegetation?",
        options: ["Desert", "Rainforest", "Grassland"],
        correct_option: "Desert"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of habitat is found at the bottom of the ocean?",
        options: [ "Tundra", "Grassland","Deep sea",],
        correct_option: "Deep sea"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat is characterized by its cold temperatures and large coniferous trees?",
        options: ["Taiga", "Tropical rainforest", "Savanna"],
        correct_option: "Taiga"
    },
    {
        question: "What habitat is found at the meeting point of land and water?",
        options: ["Wetland", "Tundra", "Desert"],
        correct_option: "Wetland"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habitat is characterized by its salty water and diverse marine life?",
        options: ["Ocean", "Rainforest", "Grassland"],
        correct_option: "Ocean"
    }
];

export default HabitatsQuestions;
